

TEMITOPE SOYOYE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER • LAGOS, NIGERIA • +234 81 689 415 26

• DETAILS •

30, Shiro Street, Fadeyi Lagos Nigeria +234 81 689 415 26 herbarbie06@gmail.com

• LINKS •

Git-Hub

Twitter

<u>Linkedln</u>

• SKILLS •

Git

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

React

• HOBBIES •

Travelling
Reading innovative books
Solving Puzzles
Creative Writing

PROFILE

Passionate web developer who has grown over the years after just transitioning. I have 2 years + rounded experience in web development and user centered designs. I seek to join and contribute my expertise to the growth of an organization.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Junior Frontend Developer at Nerdyeye Tech Limited, Lagos State

August 2020 — March 2021

Worked on internal projects for the company

Collaborated with teammates to build projects

Led a team of developers during an hackathon

Front End Instructor at Nerdy Eye Tech Ltd, Lagos State

August 2020 — March 2021

Taught beginner level HTML and Css

EDUCATION

P LLB, Osun State University, Osogbo, Osun State

November 2010 — October 2015

COURSES

Front End Web Development, Nerdy Eye Tech Lt

June 2019 — December 2019

INTERNSHIPS

Intern at Nerdy Eye Tech Ltd, Lagos State

December 2019 — July 2020

¶ REFERENCES

Samuel Linus from Nerdy Eye Tech Ltd